Summary

After graduating from Auburn University in 2019 with a degree in Biological Systems Engineering, I worked as an engineering consultant in Atlanta for two years before moving back home to Birmingham. In November of 2020, I started a company, Dibs Funding, a social and seed funding platform for early stage startup founders. Though I have known how to program since I was in high school, my experience building Dibs is where I was first introduced to the world of web development. I developed the MVP for Dibs and found a new passion for designing web apps. While working on my startup, I enrolled in Georgia Tech's Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, and I am now seeking a full-time position as a software engineer.

Education

Georgia Tech Bootcamps 2021 Full Stack Web Development

Auburn University 2015-2019 Bachelors of Biosystems Engineering Minor in Business

Skills

- → UI/UX design (Figma)
- → TDD specifically using Jest
- → API development
- → SEO and accessibility
- → Working in a team environment with version control tools such as Git and GitHub
- → Technical writing

Technologies

Frontend

- → HTML
- → CSS and CSS Libraries
- → JavaScript (ES6)
- → React (with Redux and GraphQL)

Backend

- → MySQL
- → MongoDB

Cloud

- → Heroku
- → Netlify

Work History

UX / Web Developer, Freelance 2021-Present
Using UpWork to meet clients, I developed high fidelity prototypes and completed frontend UI/UX, web design and web development projects for my clients

Founder, Dibs Funding 2021-Present

Founded and built a social networking and fundraising web app to provide early stage startups with a platform to blog, receive feedback, and raise money to fund the upfront costs of starting their company

Project Engineer, Keck & Wood, Inc. 2019-2021 Worked on various infrastructure projects including water treatment plant design, roadway design, flood management, and city planning

Research Assistant, Auburn University 2018-2019
Worked under Dr. Lauren Beckingham to write a Matlab program that used machine learning to identify minerality in a 3D CT image from a 2D training image

Projects



DibsStartup project built, Bubble.io



Reloc8 Bootcamp project, API



Sibs p UpWork project, PI React, design

References

References available upon request. Thank you!